http://yogababy.com.au/privacy

Pregnancy/Pregnancy yogaGold CoastActive birth yoga
Active Birth/Pregnancy Birth Skills WorkshopCouples Active Birth WorkshopPrivate SessionBetter birth bundleBirth stories
Pregnancy/Pregnancy yogaGold CoastActive birth yoga
Active Birth/Pregnancy Birth Skills WorkshopCouples Active Birth WorkshopPrivate SessionBetter birth bundleBirth stories
Privacy
yogababy is strongly committed to protecting your privacy while interacting with our content, products and services. We want to provide a safe and secure environment for you and your children.yogababy is concerned about protecting the safety and privacy of young people using our services. We encourage you to participate in your child's online experience.The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to tell you what kind of information we may gather about you when you visit our site, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct this information. Our policy allows you to choose what kind and how much information you provide to us and to control how we use whatever information you give us. Our goal is to provide you with a satisfying experience while allowing you to control your privacy and to give you a means to voice any questions or concerns you may have.This policy applies only to yogababy and not to other companies' or organisations' websites to which yogababy is linked.Collection of informationInformation is collected from you primarily to make it easier and more rewarding for you to use our services. Depending on the service you are accessing, you could be asked to provide information such as your name, email address or information about what you like and do not like. It is entirely your choice whether to respond to these questions or not.yogababy collects two types of information. The first type is anonymous information. For instance, we may collect information to tell us that five thousand people visit this Privacy Policy today, but we do not know their names, where they live or their date of birth - they are 'anonymous' to us. Many of the individuals who access our services are anonymous to us.The second type of information that yogababy collects is personal information. yogababy will collect personal information that lets us know the specifics of who you are such as your name, email address or postal address, when you provide it to us. With this information, yogababy can provide a variety of personalised and enhanced services that are not available to anonymous users. We hope that you will find it beneficial to provide individually identifiable information about yourself to us because it will make our services more valuable to you.Sometimes, we may specifically ask for personal information about you when you sign up to use a service. Certain information may be required, such as your name, age, internet address or screen name, billing address, type of computer, credit card number, in order to provide that service or product to you. This information may also be used to inform you of additional products and services which may interest you. You can choose not to receive such information when you are undertaking product or service registration on our website. We may also ask about your interests, but it is your choice whether to respond.How much of your personal information that you choose to disclose to yogababy is completely up to you. The only way we know something about you personally is if you provide it to us, for example when you take part in a discussion forum.Use of anonymous informationyogababy automatically gathers anonymous information to monitor the use of yogababy like the numbers and frequency of visitors to yogababy and its areas, very much like television ratings that tell the networks how many people tuned in to a program. We only use such data in the aggregate. This collective data helps us determine how much our audiences use parts of the site, so we can improve yogababy to ensure that it is as appealing as we can make it for as many users as possible. yogababy may publish or provide this aggregate data to other people.Use of personal informationyogababy will only use the personal information you have chosen to provide us for the purpose for which you provided it. yogababy will not use it for any other purpose without your consent.CookiesThe yogababy Shop site currently uses cookies.DisclosureThere will be occasions where it will be necessary for yogababy to disclose your personal information to third parties. yogababy may be required by law to disclose the information, or yogababy may be required to disclose your personal information to third parties to provide the service you have requested. For example, if you purchase products online from the yogababy Shop, yogababy will need to disclose your personal information to third parties in order to bill and deliver your products. However, the disclosure will only be made where it is necessary to fulfil the purpose for which you disclosed your personal information. Otherwise than stated above, we do not disclose personal information that you may give us, such as your name, address, email address or telephone number, to any organisation or person outside yogababy unless you have authorised us to do so. For example, when you contribute to an online forum you may want to publish your name and email address.No sale of personal informationUnder no circumstances will yogababy sell or receive payment for licensing or disclosing your personal information.Interacting with yogababyThere are many interactive features on yogababy that you can contribute to. These include: Forums, Reviews, Online Voting, Community, Mailing Lists and Email.When interacting with yogababy, we suggest that you use your discretion and exercise caution when providing your personal information.Note that whenever you post personal information in publicly accessible places, such as chat rooms or message boards, this information becomes available to anyone with access to the internet. This information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Therefore, we recommend that you refrain from posting any information that you do not want seen in these public areas. For example, when participating in a yogababy forum, your name will appear on the message board. If you do not want your real name to appear use a false name but do not under any circumstances use somebody else's name.Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any personal information. Be responsible whenever you are online.Access and correction: personal dataIf yogababy holds your personal information yogababy will where possible provide you with access to the information. yogababy will take reasonable steps to correct the information so that it is accurate, complete and up to date.Securityyogababy uses a secure data network that are designed to protect your privacy and security.Complaints about privacyIf you have any complaints relating to online privacy issues on our websites, please notify yogababy at webmaster@yogababy.com.au. While yogababy accepts no liability for any material or links posted to the service, we will investigate all complaints.Changes to yogababy privacy policyIf we decide to change the yogababy Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here.
Fertility/Fertility yoga
Pregnancy/Pregnancy yogaGold CoastActive birth yoga
Active Birth/Pregnancy Birth Skills WorkshopCouples Active Birth WorkshopPrivate SessionBetter birth bundleBirth stories
baby/Mums and Bubs Yoga
ONLINE/
Training/For Yoga TeachersFor Midwives
Shop/
Blog/
Contact Us/ContactTeachersPrivacySite search
yogababy
yogababy is a yoga school specialising in Fertility yoga, Pregnancy yoga, Natural Childbirth Education and Postnatal yoga.
Calendar
yogababy Blog
Dec 8, 2020
Suzanne Swan
I didn’t think it was possible to love a tiny human as much!
Dec 8, 2020
Suzanne Swan
Nothing I read or anything anyone told me could have prepared me for birth, it was short but intense. Thanks again for all the yoga classes and breathing. Like so many people said you’ll do all this preparation but it just depends on the day! Georgina is doing really well and we’re over the moon. I didn’t think it was possible to love a tiny human as much.
Dec 8, 2020
Suzanne Swan
Nov 25, 2020
Suzanne Swan
Rachael's challenging & rewarding natural birth
Nov 25, 2020
Suzanne Swan
My biggest driver for having a natural birth was to improve my chances of breast feeding and I’m pleased to say our little Oscar is thriving, putting on a kilogram in his first month of life with exclusive breastfeeding. It was such a challenging time but you helped us be as prepared as possible. We can’t thank you enough!
Nov 25, 2020
Suzanne Swan
FacebookGet our updates!
Email Address
Sign Up
We respect your privacy.
Thank you!
FertilityPregnancyBirthBirth education workshopsPostnatalContact us
